Charlotte Asencio

CONTACT

252-903-1274

charlotte.e.asencio@ gmail.com

charlotteasencio.com

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Social Work
Honors College
Belmont University, Nashville, TN

CERTIFICATIONS

Full Stack Web Development Certificate

The Coding Bootcamp at UNC Charlotte

SKILLS

Fluent in Spanish

CONNECT



in www.linkedin.com/in/charlotteasencio

ABOUT ME

As a developer with a background in Social Work, I am especially interested in the way technology can improve the world. I'm primarily a Front-End Developer with experience using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and various frameworks to build responsive web applications.

SIMILAR WORK EXPERIENCE

Study Programmer I
Clinical Ink

June 2018-Present Winston-Salem, NC

- Design and Build electronic source documents for clinical trials according to specifications
- Program functionality and scoring into source documents utilizing C# and JavaScript

PROJECTS

Proof of Concept Clinical Ink

- Worked on the front-end for a proof of concept project for new internal software initiative
- Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Angular, Angular Material

Pay It Forward

Coding Bootcamp at UNC Charlotte

- A web app that allows volunteer organizations to connect with volunteers
- that are searching for volunteer opportunities
- Technologies used: React.js, JSX, CSS, Firebase Database, Firebase
- Authentification

Helping Hands

Coding Bootcamp at UNC Charlotte

- An early version of the Pay It Forward project that allowed anyone to post or sign up for opportunities with no differentiation between user roles and permissions
- Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Node.js, Express, Handlebars, MySql

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Victim Services Coordinator
Forsyth County District Attorney's Office

April 2016-May 2018 Winston-Salem, NC

Support Team CoordinatorSafe Passage/ Camino Seguoro

Feb 2015-June 2015 Guatemala City, Guatemala